[OVERDO]
[Episode 19]
How is it?
We need to take the bus?
Where to?
Home.
Before the orphanage,
didn't you always live on the wharf?
My family,
like most families on wharves,
made a living from water transport.
My father worked on boats all year round,
and my mother did odd jobs to help out.
We weren't rich,
but it was stable
and peaceful.
Every time my father
came back from a trip,
he'd bring me little trinkets.
My mother was a great cook.
Every spring,
she'd make me
pork soup with bamboo shoots,
Yanduxian.
Even after all these years,
when I barely remember
what she looked like,
I still remember
the taste of that soup.
Papa!
Papa, Mama wants you back for dinner!
Papa, Papa!
Mama wants you back for dinner!
Set sail!
Go, go!
Sail!
-Sail!
-Go!
Go!
Go to Chonghai County!
What do you mean Chonghai County?
My baby's boat is
going to Spain
and America!
Papa,
when I grow up,
I want to be a captain,
traveling the world!
Travel the world!
What's wrong,
Sweetie?
But the captains
on your wharf always
leave for months at a time.
I want to be with you and Mama forever.
Don't worry.
When the time comes,
our whole family
will be on your ship.
I'll be your first mate,
and Mama your second mate.
Our family
will never ever be apart,
okay?
Okay!
Good girl.
If you two
really care about me,
hurry home and eat now.
You'll be good and eat your food,
and Papa will wash the dishes.
Then you can go back
to your world-traveling
daydreams, okay?
Okay!
Your Mama's right.
How can you be the greatest captain
if you don't eat well?
Be a great captain!
Our baby will succeed!
I'm glad you
opened up to me about this.
I just suddenly got reminded of it.
And then?
What happened after?
Later, due to an accident,
I lost my family.
And then,
I became Fang Mulan.
But the person I knew
has always been Ren Susu.
But you've never known
the real Ren Susu...
The Ren Susu who
grew up carefree
by her parents' side 12 years ago.
After entering the orphanage,
She was shattered
and ruined
by those demons.
Ever since then,
my heart's been consumed by revenge.
For revenge,
I turned into a person full of lies,
with blood on my hands.
I really don't know what
my parents would think
if they saw who I am now.
Are you trying to say
that the innocent,
brave, wise,
and kind
Ren Susu I know
isn't the real you?
Then tell me,
what's the real you
actually like?
What I'm actually like...
I've long forgotten.
Anyway...
Do you feel that
you've forgotten your past self
and gotten used to this current self
who doesn't deserve to be loved?
Haven't I also once...
felt that I don't deserve to be loved?
Mother,
Qingyi's also a biological son
of the Murong family.
Why can't he stay at home?
He caused your father's death.
Keeping him here
will only bring misfortune to our family.
Are you going to send him back
to the Li family?
Do you think they still want him?
Fine.
If no one wants him,
I'll take this little brother.
You won't have to worry about him.
You and I have
always been cut from the same cloth...
Unwanted
and unvalued.
How could I not understand?
Don't speak of yourself like this
in front of me again.
It just feels like
you're indirectly insulting me.
From now on,
Ren Susu's past is known
not only to you
but also to me.
So she still exists within you.
When the Huos are dealt with,
I want to be Ren Susu again...
and do what she truly wants to do.
What does Ren Susu truly want to do?
I guess
it must be about me.
Don't flatter yourself.
When you left me to confront the Huos,
I knew you
couldn't bear to lose me.
It's you dying I can't bear,
not losing you.
♪ Running toward you ♪
♪ From the day I thought ♪
♪ I succeeded in forgetting you ♪
♪ Facing the past ♪
♪ With you inside ♪
♪ My resolve crumbles ♪
♪ Immediately ♪
Isn't me dying and you losing me
♪ You're becoming clear ♪
the same thing?
♪ So far yet so clear ♪
Can't you say something nice to me
♪ Ever since forgetting you ♪
for a change?
♪ Became second nature ♪
What does it
matter to you?
Of course it matters.
♪ I still can't erase ♪
If you say nice things,
♪ Completely erase ♪
I'll be very happy.
♪ The certainty of my hand in yours ♪
♪ You are so clear ♪
♪ So close and so clear ♪
Can you give me a little more time?
♪ If you possibly still have the courage ♪
Let me find the Ren Susu in me back.
Of course.
♪ Then take me away from here ♪
♪ Having loved you deeply ♪
♪ Was the best decision I've made ♪
I had Lieutenant Wei
release Laiyi.
It was so dangerous today.
Why'd you have to get involved?
For her, of course.
You have absolutely
no reservations now, huh?
Qingyu,
the dust has settled.
It's time
for you to let go.
The engagement is still on.
I've talked it over with Mother.
Tomorrow,
I'll take her to try on wedding dresses.
You stay home and recover.
When you're recovered,
I'll send you abroad.
The engagement is still on?
Qingyu,
you already know she's Ren Susu.
Why do you still insist on marrying her?
For three years, she acted recklessly
in her bid to take on the Huos.
If I don't keep her by my side,
how many more lives
do you have to give her?
Her moving back into our home
is to prepare for the wedding.
Who she marries
isn't up to you.
It's up to her!
Murong Qingyi,
even if you want to throw yourself at her,
what else can you do for her right now
besides taking a bullet?
The downfall of the Huos today
wasn't because of your few punches
but the influence and prestige
of our Murong family.
I don't have to force her.
She knows what to choose.
Miss Fang,
there's a call for you.
Notify Yinwei
to find him.
Principal,
Inspector Li sent word.
Master Huo's broken out of prison.
Seal off the wharves
and block off all intersections.
None may exit the Huo residence
after entry.
Yes.
Stop right there.
With me around,
it'll never be your turn to play the hero.
Wow, aren't you a mastermind?
You make it seem like
I'm absolute trash
without the Murong title.
I'll prove to you that
even without the Murongs' backing,
I can still help her fulfill her wish.
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
You'll never get it, Qingyu.
You and I...
have never been cut from the same cloth.
To abandon the love of my life
for the sake of my family
would be to
destroy my soul.
What are you trying to say?
Qingyu,
I don't know what you're thinking,
but I know
Ms. Ye must be...
very sad.
Where's Qingyi?
I need to talk to you.
Congrats, Young Master.
You're becoming more and more
like your mother.
You know how much he looks up to you,
yet time and again,
you crush and interfere with
his choices.
Is he really your brother,
or just a tool you use
to spruce up the Murongs' image?
Who are you to
judge my relationship with Qingyi?
He can like any woman,
but absolutely not someone
as dangerous as you.
Do you think that
now that you've had your revenge,
you can pick up where you left off
with Qingyi
and rekindle your old romance?
So, in your eyes,
women like us spend our lives
seeking for
nothing but to date
noble heirs, huh?
You're spitting on everything
we've been through all these years.
For someone like you,
justice is just a concept you learned.
But for people like us,
justice is a luxury
we fight for with blood and tears.
You'll never understand this.
But Qingyi does.
I want to go back to being myself.
Fang Mulan,
in your dreams.
I'm Ren Susu.
I'm done being Fang Mulan.
Precisely because you're Ren Susu,
you must
stay by my side.
The engagement isn't yours to decide.
Master Fang's also in Nancheng.
I'll get him to come talk to you tomorrow.
Twelve years ago,
in a big fire at Wucongkou Wharf,
Ren Changhe...
Papa! Mama! Papa! Mama!
Papa! Mama!
Young Master Qingyi,
please spare me.
Spare you?
If you tell the truth later,
I might consider it.
But if
Master Huo manages to escape,
you'll bear the consequences alone.
Qingyi.
Okay,
I'll tell you everything I know.
He wants to flee abroad.
But all the wharfs in Nancheng
have been sealed off by you.
He's heading to Hangcheng
with his men.
He plans to flee
by boat from there.
Qingyi!
[Murong Residence]
Fuzi.
Young Master.
Where's Miss Fang?
She went out earlier.
Qingyi, if we don't
leave now,
we won't get to Hangcheng before dark.
It's important.
Get a pen and paper.
Okay.
If I startled you,
please accept the enclosed leaf
of Beicheng's autumn
as a token of my apology.
[Murong Residence]
Miss Fang, you're finally back.
Young Master Qingyi told me to
give this to you before he left.
Before he left?
Huo Shaoxiong's escaped.
I'm going to put an end to this.
Don't worry.
I'll be back before the first snow.
P.S.
contact me if you need anything.
P.P.S.
contact me even just to say hi.
Ren Changhe
made a living from water transport
at the wharves.
Twelve years ago,
in a big fire at Wucongkou Wharf,
over 30 people died in the fire.
This included Ren Changhe
and his wife Shao Huilan.
After the fire,
their only daughter, Ren Susu,
was taken into Renxin Orphanage.
Stop talking.
I already...
know all this.
There's more you don't know.
What's this?
[Current Affairs Daily]
[Bloodshed at Railway Celebration:
Marshal Murong Meets With Misfortune]
After the Wucongkou Wharf fire,
there was an explosion at the inauguration
ceremony of the North-South Railway.
My father
died on the spot.
It must be related to this case.
Afterwards,
the mastermind behind it wasn't found.
Only one thing was found out:
the explosive was RDX.
It's a new type of explosive from abroad.
But the key is that
this batch of explosives was
handled at Wucongkou Wharf.
Are you saying
my parents' death
wasn't an accident?
No one's ever connected
the Wucongkou Wharf fire
and the railway explosion
together before.
But now it seems that
perhaps the Wucongkou Wharf fire
was to preemptively destroy
crucial evidence of the railway explosion.
Someone wanted to silence them?
But my parents were just ordinary folk.
How could they be involved in this?
[Marshal Murong, clad in ceremonial garb,
was about to cut the ribbon and speak]
Who benefits from...
Marshal Murong's death?
Li Rongzhang.
[P.S. contact me if you need anything.]
[P.P.S. contact me even just to say hi.]
Qingyi, what should I do?
Master, careful.
Hurry.
Why so slow? Faster!
Hurry!
[Hangcheng Wharf]
Master, be careful.
Come on.
Here.
Hoist the sails.
Set sail!
Master,
good thing you were prepared,
so we could save our assets.
Once we get through this,
our Huo family
will prevail, powerful as ever.
Why's it so light?
Master,
this is...
Master, the money...
has all turned into joss paper.
Where's my money? Where is it!
Master Huo.
Setting sail so late at night,
where are you going?
It's you, you bastard!
In such a hurry, you might've
not prepared your own joss paper,
so I brought some gifts for you.
Do you like them?
Three years ago, you ruined my left hand.
Over the years...
the spasms, the tremors,
and the piercing pain
have tortured me nonstop.
Master Huo...
now,
your left hand
can feel my pain too, right?
What black magic
did you use on me?
Not me
but her.
Knowing Master Huo,
he won't surrender easily.
Even if he finds a chance to escape,
we can't let him off.
This hallucinatory drug
magnifies pain and injury,
until he dies of terror.
You two animals!
Over a decade ago,
when you spilled your first drop of blood,
you should've expected this day.
I won't...
let you two go.
Trying to provoke me
so I'd shoot you for a quick death?
That'd be letting you off too easy.
[Zhenhua No. 1 Aviation School]
I've had people look into it.
The Huo family
has always held the outside shares
for Baohua Firm,
where your father worked.
With the fall of the Huos,
some news
finally came to light.
We also found letters
between the Huos and various parties,
and discovered that before the explosion,
they were in close contact
with Li Rongzhang.
I didn't expect it either.
Back then, although the Lis and our family
were fighting for control of the railway,
after the explosion,
Li Rongzhang was also implicated.
He almost
lost command of the army.
In that case,
why'd he hurt others
when he gets nothing out of it?
We kept investigating along this line
and found that the explosives
were indeed supplied by
Li Rongzhang's partner,
an overseas arms supplier.
Since the explosives were transported
through Wucongkou Wharf
and Baohua Firm was also involved,
Li Rongzhang had every reason
to silence them,
killing dozens of innocent people,
including the Ren family.
-That means...
-That means that
if you want revenge,
you have to kill Qingyi's adoptive father,
that is Boze's biological father.
What,
want revenge?
I'll offer you a choice.
Our wedding will be
your best chance to
assassinate Li Rongzhang.
Even if I succeed,
I can't escape the Lis' retaliation.
I'll most likely die on the spot.
You want revenge
but you're afraid of death?
Ren Susu,
you're unlike your old self.
I see.
This matter is deeply interconnected
and full of perils.
You don't want a ticking time bomb like me
staying by Qingyi's side.
Will you only join forces with me
if I leave Qingyi?
Or would you
rather I fight Li Rongzhang to the death,
since my death...
would be best for Qingyi?
I don't need your help,
and I'm not leaving Qingyi.
As for my parents' revenge,
I will bide my time.
Who will let you bide your time?
The Fang family
or Qingyi?
If you're not Fang Mulan,
why involve the Fang family
in something so dangerous
like Li Rongzhang's assassination?
Well,
if you can't seek help
from the Fangs, then Qingyi?
Do I need to remind you?
Li Rongzhang doesn't treat Qingyi well,
but he's still his adoptive father.
What gives you the right to make Qingyi
commit patricide for you?
Without the Fang family,
without Qingyi,
what do you, the orphan Ren Susu, have?
Your life's all you have, isn't it?
At the wedding, even if I succeed in
assassinating Li Rongzhang and die,
you can't escape involvement.
What do you want out of this?
Now that the Huos are destroyed,
the power in Nancheng will be reshuffled.
If you assassinate Li Rongzhang,
the power of both the Huos and the Lis
will fall into my hands.
Do you really think I believe that
you're this power-hungry?
Believe it or not,
now, you just need to choose
if you'll shoulder
the Rens' grudge or not.
Principal,
assassinating Li Rongzhang
is immensely dangerous,
and Miss Fang's just a weak woman...
So what?
Regardless of her doubts, this is
an inevitable path she has to take.
Even if we don't consider
Miss Fang's life,
it isn't do or die
between us and Li Rongzhang yet.
Killing him now for past events...
Principal,
you're not a rash person.
There's a reason he must die.
But he's still
Young Master Qingyi's adoptive father
and Young Master Boze's biological father.
If one day they find out
it was you who ordered
Miss Fang to assassinate Li Rongzhang,
your brotherhood
will most likely be ruined.
When the edifice is collapsing,
I can only prioritize the bigger picture.